{"data":[{"question":"He drank two pints of beer.' 'What! He drank _______!'","a":"two litres","b":"a litre","c":"four litres","d":"half a litre","answer":"2","explain":"\n-1 US pint = 473.176473 milliliters","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"______ did you say she is?","a":"How weight","b":"How heavy","c":"What heavy","d":"What weight","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- How heavy: how much does it weigh","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This tank holds ten gallons. Yes, it's a _______.","a":"ten-gallons-tank","b":"ten-gallon tank","c":"ten gallon tank","d":"tank of ten gallon","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular)+unit \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This bag is too _______ for the child.","a":"weight","b":"weigh","c":"weights","d":"heavy","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Too + adj + for somebody to do some thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She is worried, she keeps gaining ______.","a":"weight","b":"weighes","c":"weighs","d":"weightes","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Gain weight","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"That man is English. He weighs 12 _______ 4 lbs.","a":"stones","b":"stone","c":"quarters","d":"hundredweights","answer":"2","explain":"- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms\u00a0\n- The plural form of stone is correctly stone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"My friend is very big. He weighs ________.","a":"50 stones","b":"14 stone","c":"13 stones","d":"5 stone","answer":"2","explain":"- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms\u00a0\n- The plural form of stone is correctly stone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"There are 14 pounds in ________.","a":"a stone","b":"two stones","c":"two stone","d":"two-stones","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms \n- 1 pound = 453.59237 grams","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"\nThere is _______ truck just behind us.","a":"five tons","b":"five ton","c":"five-ton","d":"ton-five","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A ______ lorry is following us.","a":"twenty tons","b":"twenty-ton","c":"twenty ton","d":"ton-twenty","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}